b2byellowpages.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy at b2bYellowpages.com

Privacy Policy

 **This Privacy Policy was last modified March 13, 2009**

The following policy applies to all the websites owned and operated by b2bBiz.com, Inc., the parent corporation of b2bYellowpages.com on the World Wide Web.

This policy covers how b2bBiz.com, Inc., hereinafter referred to as "b2bYellowpages.com", treats information including personal information that b2bYellowpages.com collects and receives. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, phone number, company name, company website as well as information that is not otherwise publicly available.

All products, services, features and information on b2bYellowpages.com are made available subject to this Privacy Policy. By using this site you expressly agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

This website contains links and advertising to other websites. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that b2bYellowpages.com does not own or control, or to people that b2bYellowpages.com does not employ or manage. The policies of these companies, advertisers, their websites and employees may significantly differ from that of the b2bYellowpages.com website. It is your responsibility to contact such companies, web site operators or advertisers directly to view and determine their privacy policies. 

**What information do we collect?**

b2bYellowpages.com serves a general audience primarily geared toward businesses that advertise to, or are seeking products, services and information from other businesses. Information from all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy.

b2bYellowpages.com is committed to respecting your privacy. b2bYellowpages.com does not collect any unique information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Whenever you visit b2bYellowpages.com, our web server logs automatically receive and record general information from your web browser including your IP Address, time of day, browser type, browser language, pages viewed and any search terms you query. 

b2bYellowpages.com collects personal information when you register with b2bYellowpages.com for any of its memberships, products, services, features or directory listings. When you register we ask for information such as your name, company, phone, email address, address, zip code, title, industry, etc. Upon registration and log-in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

b2bYellowpages.com uses all information to customize your experience and to improve our services. The data of our members, customers and viewers are collected and processed in one or more databases maintained directly or indirectly by b2bYellowpages.com.

 **b2bYellowpages.com uses cookies.**

A "cookie" is a piece of data that identifies you and/or your computer as a unique user. Internet cookies could save the pages of our web site viewed by a visitor or user, a members password and user name upon log-in as well as the advertisements clicked upon. 

The cookies enable b2bYellowpages.com to personalize its web site for each visitor. When the visitor uses or re-visits our web site, b2bYellowpages.com will recognize information about the user by the Internet cookie and customize the visitors experience accordingly. Internet cookies are stored on the visitors hard drive and are not stored in any form on any equipment owned by b2bYellowpages.com. You can edit your browser so as not to accept our cookies, but features of the web site may not function properly if you do not accept the cookies. 

Advertisers or other companies do not have access to the b2bYellowpages.com cookies. b2bYellowpages.com lets other companies that show advertisements on our pages set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not b2bYellowpages.com. Google is a third party vendor who use [DoubleClick DART cookies](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to b2bYellowpages.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**With whom does b2bYellowpages.com share the collected information?**

* b2bYellowpages.com may share information about our users and search trends with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. The collective data that we share with our working partners and our affiliates helps us to provide you with better products and services.   

* b2bYellowpages.com believes it is necessary to also share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the b2bYellowpages.com terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  

* Co-registration membership information. b2bYellowpages.com partners with companies that allow us to provide additional products, services, features or bonuses to our viewers and members. Depending upon our partnership agreement, some partners will advertise our services and provide viewers with a code that is unique to that partner. The code allows bonuses to be added to a membership once an authorized code is entered and a successful membership registration application is completed. By entering an authorized code, you agree to co-registration. Co-registration permits b2bYellowpages.com to share your personal registration information with our partners. The personally identifiable information you provided during your registration process is shared with the respective partner whose code you entered. In this manner, b2bYellowpages and its partner believe we can provide even greater features to you.

You may receive information or be contacted from our co-registration partners directly. We advise you to review their privacy and data collection policies for further information as to how they utilize your information. We are not responsible for the use of your personally identifiable information by any such partner. In order to cancel your membership with any of these partners you will need to go directly to the partner.

 **Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

We reserve the right to send you an occasional communication relating to the b2bYellowpages.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages or newsletter that are considered part of your b2bYellowpages.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You can delete your b2bYellowpages.com account by utilizing the contact us link located on most web pages. In doing so, however, your listings in our web, local and B2B directory will be removed. 

**Warranty**

For all of our transaction and information processed, we employ reasonable security methods and technologies. While we strive to protect your personal information and ensure its security on the systems that we employ, unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot insure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

 **What if the privacy policy changes?**

As a result of the World Wide Web continually evolving with new technologies, security features and technologies, this Policy will change from time to time. b2bYellowpages.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Our current privacy policy practices will be accessible through the posting of a clear and conspicuous link near the bottom of most pages on our website. All changes will be posted on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect and to whom we disclose such information.

b2bYellowpages.com may also transfer any information in its possession in connection with a sale of assets of the company, a sale of the company or a merger. In this event, the information about you may become the subject to a different privacy policy. Please review our Privacy Policy on a regular basis so that you will be apprised of any changes. 

**What if I have questions or comments about this privacy policy?**

You can direct all additional questions and comments regarding our privacy policy through our **feedback form.**
